Mobius, Inc. Records MS208
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Audiovisual materials, 1968 -- 2009; MS208.008; 42.0 Linear Feet
  - VHS, U-matic and Beta-cam, 1968 -- 2003; MS208.008.002; 30.0 Linear Feet
    - Letters from Japan tape #2, 1987-04-11; MS208.008.002.081.00007; Young, Victor (Reel 81)
    - Letters from Japan tape #3, 1987-04-11; MS208.008.002.081.00008; Young, Victor (Reel 81)
    - Letters from Japan tape #4, 1987-04-11; MS208.008.002.081.00009; Young, Victor (Reel 81)
      Master U-matic Maxell KCS20 3/4 in. Four short works, Young interview, audio only.
    - Breathe don't Breathe, Dreams of Home, 1987-04-11; MS208.008.002.081.00010; Arsem, Marilyn (Reel 81)
      U-matic 3/4in Maxell KCS20. Tape 5
    - Breathe don't Breathe, Dreams of Home, 1987-04-11; MS208.008.002.081.00011; Arsem, Marilyn (Reel 81)
      U-matic 3/4in Maxell KCS20. Tape 6
    - Breathe don't Breathe, Dreams of Home, 1987-04-11; MS208.008.002.081.00012; Arsem, Marilyn (Reel 81)
      U-matic 3/4in Maxell KCS20. Tape 7
    - Breathe don't Breathe, Dreams of Home, 1987-04-11; MS208.008.002.081.00013; Arsem, Marilyn (Reel 81)
      U-matic 3/4in Maxell KCS20. Tape 8
    - 4 short works, interview with Victor Young, 1987-04-12; MS208.008.002.081.00014 (Reel 81)
      Master U-matic 3/4in Maxell KCS20. Tape 9
    - Interview with Marilyn Arsem, 1987-04-12; MS208.008.002.081.00015 (Reel 81)
      7mins, U-matic 3/4in Maxell KCS20. Tape 10Part 2 of interview.
    - Interview with Marilyn Arsem, 1987-04-12; MS208.008.002.081.00016 (Reel 81)
      22mins, U-matic 3/4in Maxell KCS20. Part 1 do interview. Tape 11
    - Lot's Wife, 1987-04-12; MS208.008.002.081.00017; Paoli, Mario (Reel 81)
      U-matic 3/4in Maxell KCS20.From 4 short works. Tape 12
    - Lot's Wife, 1987-04-12; MS208.008.002.081.00018; Paoli, Mario (Reel 81)
      U-matic 3/4in Maxell KCS20.From 4 short works. Tape 13
    - Lot's Wife, 1987-04-12; MS208.008.002.081.00019; Paoli, Mario (Reel 81)
      U-matic 3/4in Maxell KCS20.From 4 short works. Tape 14
    - Mario's Interview, 1987-04-12; MS208.008.002.081.00020; Paoli, Mario (Reel 81)
      U-matic 3/4in Maxell KCS20.From 4 short works. Tape 15
    - Mario's Interview from 4 Short Works, 1987-04-12; MS208.008.002.081.00021; Paoli, Mario (Reel 81)
      U-matic 3/4in Maxell KCS20.From 4 short works. Tape 16
    - Misuse of Tools, 1987-04-12; MS208.008.002.082.00001; Lang, Dan (Reel 82)
      U-matic 3/4in Maxell KCS20.From 4 short works. Tape 17
    - Misuse of Tools, 1987-04-12; MS208.008.002.082.00002; Lang, Dan (Reel 82)
      U-matic 3/4in Maxell KCS20.From 4 short works. Tape 18
    - Misuse of Tools, 1987-04-12; MS208.008.002.082.00003; Lang, Dan (Reel 82)
      U-matic 3/4in Maxell KCS20.From 4 short works. Tape 19
    - Dan Lang's Interview from 4 short works, 1987-04-12; MS208.008.002.082.00004; Lang, Dan (Reel 82)
      U-matic 3/4in Maxell KCS20.From 4 short works. Tape 20
    - Works in procress #22, Wakdjunkaga, the fool, 1987-04-24; MS208.008.002.082.00005; Janzen, Thomas (Reel 82)
      U-matic 3/4 in KCS20
    - Works in procress #22, Mr and Mrs Zone performance, 1987-04-24; MS208.008.002.082.00006; Barron,Harris; Barron, Ros (Reel 82)
      Dub 1/2 in VHS
    - Mobius Fundraiser. Board of Directors Party, 1987-04-25; MS208.008.002.082.00007 (Reel 82)
      Master U-matic 3/4 in KCS20.
    - Letters from Japan and Lots Wife, 1987-05; MS208.008.002.082.00008; Paoli, Mario; Young, Victor (Reel 82)
      Dub U-matic Maxell KCS 20 3/4 in. 4 Short Works excerpts.
    - Dreams of Home and Misuse of Tools, 1987-05; MS208.008.002.082.00009; Arsem, Marilyn; Lang, Dan; Young, Victor; Paoli, Mario (Reel 82)
      Edit Master U-matic Maxell KCS 20 3/4 in. 4 Short Works. No interviews.
    - Letters from Japan and Lots Wife, 1987-05; MS208.008.002.082.00010; Arsem, Marilyn; Lang, Dan; Young, Victor; Paoli, Mario (Reel 82)
      Edit Master U-matic Maxell KCS 20 3/4 in. 4 Short Works.
    - 4 short works: Breathe\Don't Breathe and The Misuse of Tools, 1987-05; MS208.008.002.082.00011; Arsem, Marilyn; Lang, Dan; Young, Victor; Paoli, Mario (Reel 82)
      Dub U-matic 3/4 in KCS20
    - 4 short works: Letters from Japan and Dreams of Home, 1987-05-21; MS208.008.002.082.00012; Young, Victor; Arsem, Marilyn (Reel 82)
      Master, U-matic 3/4 in KCS20. Rough cut and titles.
    - 4 short works: Lot's Wife and The Misuse of Tools, 1987-05-21; MS208.008.002.082.00013; Paoli, Mario; Young, Victor (Reel 82)
      U-matic 3/4 in KCS20. Rough Cut
    - Sound Art Festival, 1987-06-05 -- 1987-06-06; MS208.008.002.082.00014; Lentz,Daniel; Love, Jessica; Fischer, Linda; Rothenberg, Ellen (Reel 82)
      1/2 in VHS. Performed with Mobius Performing Group with explosion.
    - Sound Art Festival, 1987-06-06 -- 1987-06-10; MS208.008.002.082.00015; Fischer, Linda; Rothenberg, Ellen; O'Hara, Morgan; Oliveros, Pauline (Reel 82)
      1/2 in VHS
    - Sound Art Festival, 1987-06-12; MS208.008.002.082.00016; Hunt, Jerry; Plsek, Tom; Kuivila, Ron; Jonson,Larry; Roads, Curtis; Howard, Earl (Reel 82)
    - Sound Art Festival, 1987-06-13; MS208.008.002.082.00017; Hunt, Jerry; Plsek, Tom; Kuivila, Ron; Jonson,Larry; Roads, Curtis; Howard, Earl (Reel 82)
    - Sound Art Festival, Hay Installation #1, 1987-06-17; MS208.008.002.082.00018; Ewart, Douglas; Timpson, Michael (Reel 82)
    - Sound Art Festival, Hay Installation #2, 1987-06-17; MS208.008.002.082.00019; Ewart, Douglas; Timpson, Michael (Reel 82)
    - Sound Art Festival, 1987-06-19; MS208.008.002.082.00020; Driscoll, John; Moss, David (Reel 82)
    - Sound Art Festival, 1987-06-20; MS208.008.002.082.00021; Driscoll, John; Moss, David (Reel 82)
    - Slomo Silent Observations, 1987-08-31; MS208.008.002.083.00001; Arsem, Marilyn; Davis, Meredith (Reel 83)
      Master U-matic 3/4 in KCS20. At Brockton Museum.
      3/4-inch
    - Silent Observations #1, 1987-08-31; MS208.008.002.083.00002; Arsem, Marilyn; Davis, Meredith (Reel 83)
    - Silent Observations #2, 1987-08-31; MS208.008.002.083.00003; Arsem, Marilyn; Davis, Meredith (Reel 83)
    - Not Defining Performance Art, Tape 1, 1987-10-13; MS208.008.002.083.00004 (Reel 83)
      90 min. Master VHS. panel discussion.
    - Not Defining Performance Art, Tape 2, 1987-10-13; MS208.008.002.083.00005 (Reel 83)
      60 min. Master VHS. panel discussion.
    - Dreams (breathe/don't breathe) of Home, 1987-06-19; MS208.008.002.083.00006; Arsem, Marilyn (Reel 83)
      10 min. U-matic Maxell 3/4 in KCS 20. 1 minute Bars, 10 sec black, excerpts. Video by Bob Raymond.FY 89 Visual Arts Program.
    - Dies Simulation Je Suis (un readymade), 1988-01; MS208.008.002.083.00007; Britton,Ben (Reel 83)
      t30 VHS. Dub?
    - Vessel #1, 1988-01-02; MS208.008.002.083.00008; Delahunta, Scott (Reel 83)
      Master. U-matic Maxell KCS20 3/4 in. First half (other half missing)
    - Vessel #2, 1988-01-04; MS208.008.002.083.00009; Delahunta, Scott (Reel 83)
      Master. U-matic Maxell KCS20 3/4 in. #1 day 2, first run through.
    - Vessel #3, 1988-01-04; MS208.008.002.083.00010; Delahunta, Scott (Reel 83)
      Master. U-matic Maxell KCS20 3/4 in. #2 day 2, first run through.
    - Vessel #4, 1988-01-04; MS208.008.002.083.00011; Delahunta, Scott (Reel 83)
      Master. U-matic Maxell KCS20 3/4 in. #3 day 2, first run through (9-10) minutes and tape a of second run through.
    - Vessel #5, 1988-01-04; MS208.008.002.083.00012; Delahunta, Scott (Reel 83)
      Master. U-matic Maxell KCS20 3/4 in. Tape b of second run through.
    - Vessel #6, 1988-01-04; MS208.008.002.083.00013; Delahunta, Scott (Reel 83)
      Master. U-matic Maxell KCS20 3/4 in. Tape c of second run through.
    - Drought Scott DeLaHunta rehearsal, 1988-01-05; MS208.008.002.083.00014; Delahunta, Scott; Raymond; Plsek; Vasello (Reel 83)
      Master. U-matic Maxell KCS20 3/4 in.
    - Drought DeLaHunta rehearsal #2, 1988-01-05; MS208.008.002.083.00015; Delahunta, Scott; Raymond; Plsek; Vasello (Reel 83)
    - 4 short works, Letters from Japan, and Lot's Wife, 1988-01-07; MS208.008.002.083.00016; Mobius Performing Group (Reel 83)
      Dub. U-matic Maxell KCS20 3/4 in
    - Drought Scott DeLaHunta Tape # 1, 1988-01-09; MS208.008.002.083.00017; Delahunta, Scott; Raymond; Plsek; Vasello (Reel 83)
      U-matic Maxell KCS20 3/4 in
    - Drought Scott DeLaHunta rehearsal #2, 1988-01-09; MS208.008.002.083.00018; Delahunta, Scott (Reel 83)
    - Drought Scott DeLaHunta rehearsal tape 3, 1988-01-09; MS208.008.002.083.00019; Delahunta, Scott (Reel 83)
    - Persephone and Hades, 1988-02-11; MS208.008.002.084.00001; Arsem, Marilyn; Miller, David; Novotny-Jones, Mari; Lydenberg (Reel 84)
      Dub U-matic Maxell KCS20 3/4 in
    - Persephone and Hades, 1985; MS208.008.002.084.00002 (Reel 84)
      Master U-matic Sony 3/4 in KCS-20BRK
    - Leaving/going home (two versions), 1988-02-17 -- 1988-02-27; MS208.008.002.084.00003; Arsem, Marilyn (Reel 84)
      Dub VHS. Doc of 2 live Perf. Two versions.Leaving/Going Home Works in Progress, Domestic Trilogy. Videotape Mari Novotny-Jones and Bob Raymond.
    - Works in Progress #24, 1988-02-27; MS208.008.002.084.00004; Pugh, Mark; Sciscenti,Steve; Bowman, Odell; Arsem, Marilyn (Reel 84)
      Master VHS Leaving/ Going Home
    - Writing about Performance Art: Panel discussion, 1988-03-08; MS208.008.002.084.00005 (Reel 84)
      Master VHS. Tape 1.
    - Writing about Performance Art: Panel discussion, 1988-03-08; MS208.008.002.084.00006 (Reel 84)
      Master VHS. Tape 2.
    - Changing Room: Living in Sin(e), 1988-03-18; MS208.008.002.084.00007; Arsem, Marilyn; Raymond, Bob (Reel 84)
      Master? VHS. At Boston film and video foundation.
    - A funky copy of Marilyn and Schula (MNJ), 1988-05-06; MS208.008.002.084.00008; Arsem, Marilyn; Novotny-Jones, Mari (Reel 84)
      SVHS. On BNN TV about fundraiser party and MAG
    - Critic of God, 1988-05-22; MS208.008.002.084.00009; Lang, Dan (Reel 84)
      Master VHS
    - Pacific Transducer series Perf #1, 1988-06-03; MS208.008.002.084.00010; Lerman, Richard; Raymond, Bob (Reel 84)
      Master VHS. Mobius / Raymond, Bob Performance Documentation
    - Pacific Transducer series Perf #2, 1968-06-04; MS208.008.002.084.00011; Lerman, Richard; Paoli, Mario (Reel 84)
      Master VHS. Cam Mario Paoli
    - 7 yellow actions in Cohasset, 1988-06-25; MS208.008.002.084.00012; Arsem, Marilyn (Reel 84)
      Master 1/2 in VHS. 46 mins. Cohasset
    - Audience of one - 13 Actions in Yellow, 1988-06-25 -- 1988-06-26; MS208.008.002.084.00013; Arsem, Marilyn (Reel 84)
      Master Edit 1/2 in VHS. Perf and 10 minutes of Interviews. Mark Palmgren, Teil Silverstein, Emily Prince, Sarah Griffith, James Williams, mark. Perf: Joan, tea party, lemons.
    - Audience of one - 13 Actions in Yellow, 1988-06-25 -- 1988-06-26; MS208.008.002.084.00014; Arsem, Marilyn (Reel 84)
      1/2 in VHS. 32:10 min. ten min interviews. Rough cuts.
    - Drought studio work tape 2 - 2243, 1988-09-25; MS208.008.002.084.00015; DeLaHunta; Raymond; Plsek; Vasello (Reel 84)
      U-matic Sony 3/4in KCS-20BRK Shot list included.DeLaHunta/Raymond/Plsek/Vasello collaboration
    - Drought studio work tape 1 - 2243, 1988-09-25; MS208.008.002.084.00016; DeLaHunta; Raymond; Plsek; Vasello (Reel 84)
      U-matic Sony 3/4in KCS-20BRK Shot list included.
    - Drought #1 Edit master 2283, 1988-09-29; MS208.008.002.084.00017; DeLaHunta; Raymond; Plsek; Vasello (Reel 84)
      Edit Master U-matic Sony 3/4in KCS-20BRK
    - Drought 10/20 tape 1, 1988-10-20; MS208.008.002.084.00018; DeLaHunta; Raymond; Plsek; Vasello (Reel 84)
      U-matic Sony 3/4in KCS-20BRK Shot list included. Time code 00.
    - Drought 2 10/20 tape 2, 1988-10-20; MS208.008.002.084.00019; DeLaHunta; Raymond; Plsek; Vasello (Reel 84)
      U-matic Sony 3/4in KCS-20BRK. About 14 minutes Shot list included. Time code 01.
    - Drought 10/20 tape 3 (blue ink) 02 (black ink), 1988-10-20; MS208.008.002.084.00020; DeLaHunta; Raymond; Plsek; Vasello (Reel 84)
      U-matic Sony 3/4in KCS-20BRK. Face close up Shot list included. Tape 3 face close up time code 02
    - Drought 10/27 #1 studio branches, 1988-10-27; MS208.008.002.084.00021; DeLaHunta; Raymond; Plsek; Vasello (Reel 84)
      U-matic Sony 3/4in KCS-20BRK. Studio branches. Shot list included. Time code 03.
    - Drought 10/27 #2 2291, 1988-10-27; MS208.008.002.085.00001; DeLaHunta; Raymond; Plsek; Vasello (Reel 85)
      U-matic Sony 3/4in KCS-20BRK. Studio flowers & branches. Shot list included. Time code 04.
    - Drought 10/27 tape 3, 1988-10-27; MS208.008.002.085.00002; DeLaHunta; Raymond; Plsek; Vasello (Reel 85)
      U-matic Sony 3/4in KCS-20BRK. Studio flowers & branches. Shot list included. Time code 05.
    - Drought Studio Shoot Tape 1, 1988-11-14; MS208.008.002.085.00003; DeLaHunta; Raymond; Plsek; Vasello (Reel 85)
      U-matic Sony 3/4in KCS-20BRK. Studio shoots. Tape one. Shot list included. Time code 07.
    - Drought Studio Shoot Tape 2, 1988-11-14; MS208.008.002.085.00004; DeLaHunta; Raymond; Plsek; Vasello (Reel 85)
      U-matic Sony 3/4in KCS-20BRK. Studio shoots. Tape two. Shot list included. Time code 08.
    - Panel Discussion: Dance/video collaborations, 1988-11-30; MS208.008.002.085.00005; Delahunta, Scott; Raymond,Bob; Josa Jones,Paula; Sebring, Ellen; Zawerucha, Stefa; Ashworth, Cat; Fritz, Davis; Berry,Ethan (Reel 85)
      Master VHS. Ethan Berry moderator. Scott DeLaHunta, Bob Raymond,Paula Josa Jones, Ellen Sebring, Stefa Zawerucha, Cat Ashworth, Davis Fritz
    - Drought Digital Projection Master w/ Analog Tracks and audio edit, 1988-11-30; MS208.008.002.085.00006; DeLaHunta; Raymond; Plsek; Vasello (Reel 85)
      Master/Digital VHS. Digital protection master w/ analog tracks.Fuji 1/2 in Super Xgrid Pro t120 SP PCM. Note in original inventory said "I Believe there is an exact copy with the word PROJECTION in title "
    - Drought Audio Edit, 1988-11-30; MS208.008.002.085.00007; DeLaHunta; Raymond; Plsek; Vasello (Reel 85)
      Master VHS. Fuji 1/2 in Super Xgrid Pro t120 SP PCM
    - Drought:Tom Plsek Audio copy, 1988-11; MS208.008.002.085.00008; DeLaHunta; Raymond; Plsek; Vasello (Reel 85)
      VHS 1/2 in maxwell p/I plus. Has paper sound maps/ notes in sleeve
    - Drought, 1988-12-12; MS208.008.002.085.00009; Delahunta, Scott; Raymond,Bob; Plsek; Vasello (Reel 85)
      U-Matic Sony 3/4in KCS-20XBR. 10 min segment + credits. Scott deLahunta (producer,performer) and Bob Raymond (editor, video director)
    - Drought TC 19 Pittsburg St 1 Ithaca .3, 1988-12-12; MS208.008.002.085.00010; DeLaHunta; Raymond; Plsek; Vasello (Reel 85)
      U-matic Sony 3/4in KCS-20XBR. S.8 xfer (super 8 transfer). Note included.
    - Drought TC 20 Ithaca .3, 1988-12-12; MS208.008.002.085.00011; DeLaHunta; Raymond; Plsek; Vasello (Reel 85)
      U-matic Sony 3/4in KCS-20XBR Super 8 transfer. Shot list/note included.
    - Drought documentation Tape 1, 1988-12-18; MS208.008.002.085.00012; DeLaHunta; Raymond; Plsek; Vasello (Reel 85)
      U-matic Sony 3/4 in KCS20 BRK. Time code 01, 11?
    - Drought documentation Tape 2, 1988-12-18; MS208.008.002.085.00013; DeLaHunta; Raymond; Plsek; Vasello (Reel 85)
      U-matic Sony 3/4 in KCS20 BRK. Time code 02
    - Drought documentation Tape 3, 1988-12-18; MS208.008.002.085.00014; DeLaHunta; Raymond; Plsek; Vasello (Reel 85)
      U-matic Sony 3/4 in KCS20 BRK. Time code 03
    - S8 transfer GOKO Drought, 1988; MS208.008.002.085.00015; DeLaHunta; Raymond; Plsek; Vasello (Reel 85)
      Raw. U-matic Sony 3/4in KCS-20BRK. Time code 09. Shot list included.
    - S8 transfer GOKO Drought, 1988; MS208.008.002.085.00016; DeLaHunta; Raymond; Plsek; Vasello (Reel 85)
      Raw. U-matic Sony 3/4in KCS-20BRK. Time code 10. Shot list included.
    - Drought S8 transfer tape 1, 1988; MS208.008.002.085.00017; DeLaHunta; Raymond; Plsek; Vasello (Reel 85)
      Raw. U-matic Sony 3/4in KCS-20BRK. Time code 12. Shot list included.
    - Drought parts 1and4 w credits, 2nd generation edit 2335, 1988; MS208.008.002.085.00018; DeLaHunta; Raymond; Plsek; Vasello (Reel 85)
      U-matic Sony 3/4in KCS-20XBR. 21:31 mins. Excerpts from the video portion of the colab.
    - Drought parts 1 and 4, 1988; MS208.008.002.085.00019; DeLaHunta; Raymond; Plsek; Vasello (Reel 85)
      U-matic Sony 3/4in KCS-20XBR. 21:10 mins program run- time total with credits at end. 15 secs bars/tone, 7 secs black.
    - Drought sub-master, 1988 -- 1989; MS208.008.002.086.00001; Delahunta, Scott; Raymond, Bob; Plsek, Tom; Vasello (Box 86)
      Sony 3/4 inch KCS 20XBR
    - Drought parts 1 and 4, 1988; MS208.008.002.086.00002; Delahunta, Scott; Raymond, Bob; Plsek, Tom; Vasello (Box 86)
      Maxell T120 VHS
    - Drought, 1988; MS208.008.002.086.00003; Delahunta, Scott; Raymond, Bob; Plsek, Tom; Vasello (Box 86)
      Maxell GX Silver
    - Drought audio edit, 1988; MS208.008.002.086.00004; Delahunta, Scott; Raymond, Bob; Plsek, Tom; Vasello (Box 86)
      Maxell 1/2 inch T120 M20 VHS.
    - Drought S-8 Transfer, Goko, 1988; MS208.008.002.086.00005; Delahunta, Scott; Raymond, Bob; Plsek, Tom; Vasello (Box 86)
      Maxell 3/4 inch Videocassette
    - Drought S-8 Transfer Tape 3, 1988; MS208.008.002.086.00006; Delahunta, Scott; Raymond, Bob; Plsek, Tom; Vasello (Box 86)
    - Drought S-8 Transfer Tape 2, 1988; MS208.008.002.086.00007; Delahunta, Scott; Raymond, Bob; Plsek, Tom; Vasello (Box 86)
    - Drought S-8 Transfer Tape 4, 1988; MS208.008.002.086.00008; Delahunta, Scott; Raymond, Bob; Plsek, Tom; Vasello (Box 86)
    - Drought S-8 Transfer, Goko, 1988; MS208.008.002.086.00009; Delahunta, Scott; Raymond, Bob; Plsek, Tom; Vasello (Box 86)
      Maxell 3/4 inch KCS20
    - Give Me the Willies at Blacksmith House in Cambridge, 1988; MS208.008.002.086.00010; Aronstein, Jude; Allen, J. (Box 86)
    - Excerpts of 3 solo works: Blue Monday, Parlor, Fork Knife Spoon, 1988 -- 1992; MS208.008.002.086.00011; Adams, Nancy (Box 86)
    - Drought: parts 1 and 4, 1988 -- 1989; MS208.008.002.086.00012; Delahunta, Scott; Raymond, Bob; Plsek, Tom; Vasello (Box 86)
      Sony 3/4 inch KCS 20XBR. 21 minutes.
    - Drought audio edit, 1988 -- 1989; MS208.008.002.086.00013; Delahunta, Scott; Raymond, Bob; Plsek, Tom; Vasello (Box 86)
      Maxell1/2 inch T120 VHS
    - Exact Location of Soul, 1989; MS208.008.002.086.00014; Novotny-Jones, Mari (Box 86)
      Maxell 1/2 inch T60 VHS
    - The Beginning or the End, 1989; MS208.008.002.086.00015; Arsem, Marilyn; Novotny-Jones, Mari; Davis, Jessie (Box 86)
      Maxell 3/4 inch KCS20. 9 minutes.
    - The Beginning or the End original tape #3, 1989; MS208.008.002.086.00016; Arsem, Marilyn; Novotny-Jones, Mari; Davis, Jessie (Box 86)
      Sony 3/4 inch KCS 20XBR. Shot at Mobius.
    - Silent Observations, 1989; MS208.008.002.086.00017; Davis, Meredith; Raymond, Bob (Box 86)
      Maxell 1/2 inch T120 M20 VHS. 16 minutes. Video by Bob Raymond.
    - Silent Observations installation at Fuller Museum of Art, 1989; MS208.008.002.086.00018; Davis, Meredith; Arsem, Marilyn; Raymond, Bob (Box 86)
      Maxell 1/2 inch T120 VHS. Installation by Davis, performance by Arsem, video by Raymond.
    - Mobius Reviewed on WBZ-TV, 1989-09-11; MS208.008.002.087.00001; WB2 TV (Box 87)
      BASF / Meridith, Marilyn, Bob, Scott, Dan appearing
    - Where Wild Geese Fly, 1989-01-21; MS208.008.002.087.00002; Raymond, Bob; Davis, Meredith; Adams, Nancy (Box 87)
      Sony UmaticS 3/4in KCS20 / Master
    - Joan Gale's Of Tanne, 1989-01-21; MS208.008.002.087.00003; Gale, Joan; Raymond, Bob (Box 87)
      Sony UmaticS / KCS-20XBR / Master / Xfer to DV 12/13
    - Where the Wild Geese Fly, Of Tanne, 1989-01-21; MS208.008.002.087.00004; Davis, Meredith; Gale, Joan (Box 87)
      Maxell T120 / 1/2 in VHS Window dub from 3/4"
    - Leaving/Going Home 2A, 1989-01-29; MS208.008.002.087.00005; Arsem, M.; Jones, M; Davis, J.; Raymond B. (Box 87)
      Sony UmaticS / KCS-20XBR 3/4 in/ Master / Xfer to DV CAM 10/13
    - Leaving/Going Home 2B, 1989-01-29; MS208.008.002.087.00006; Arsem, M.; Jones, M; Davis, J.; Raymond B. (Box 87)
    - The Beginning or the End (Leaving/Going Home) 1B+2B, 1989-01-31; MS208.008.002.087.00007; Arsem, Marilyn (Box 87)
      Maxell T120 / 1/2 in VHS / Window dub doesn't corresp. to TC
    - The Beginning or the End (Leaving/Going Home) Rough Rough Cut, 1989-01-31; MS208.008.002.087.00008; Arsem, Marilyn (Box 87)
      Maxell T120 1/2 in VHS
    - The Beginning or the End (Leaving/Going Home) 1B+2A, 1989-01-31; MS208.008.002.087.00009; Arsem, Marilyn (Box 87)
      Maxell T120 1/2 in VHS / Window dub w/ Time Code
    - The Beginning or the End, 1989-02; MS208.008.002.087.00010; Arsem, Marilyn, Raymond, Bob (Box 87)
      Sony UmaticS / KCS-20XBR 3/4 in./ Master Edit / .05 Black, .30 Bars, .15 Black, .50 Starts, 9.28 Ends / CH1 Singing/Ambient, CH2 Synthesizer
    - The Beginning or the End, 1989-02; MS208.008.002.087.00011; Arsem, Marilyn; Davis, Jessie; Novotny-Jones, Mari; Raymond, Bob (Box 87)
      Sony UmaticS / KCS-20XBR 3/4 in./ .50 Bars+black, 9.28 Program / Studio Shot Edited Version / W Jessie Davis and MaryNJ
    - The Beginning or the End Tape 3, 1989-02 -- 1991-05; MS208.008.002.087.00012; Arsem, Marilyn; Raymond, Bob (Box 87)
      KCS-20XBR 3/4 in./ Copy (5/91) / to DVCAM 10/21 / copy for Continental Cablevision of Cambridge for programming 5/91
    - The Beginning or the End, 1989-02-17; MS208.008.002.087.00013; Arsem, Marilyn; Adams, Nancy (Box 87)
      Maxell T120 1/2 in./ 17:55 min / Live Performance / 2nd dub / w edit
    - Domestic Trilogy, 1989-02-17; MS208.008.002.087.00014; Arsem, Marilyn; Novotny-Jones, Mari (Box 87)
      Maxell T120 1/2 in./ Minus Blue Monday / Master
    - The Beginning or the End #2, 1989-02-17; MS208.008.002.087.00015; Arsem, Marilyn; Novotny-Jones, Mari; Davis, Jessie; Adams, Nancy (Box 87)
      Maxell T120 M20 1/2 in./ Performance documentation, straight, unedited / 12/24/13 Xfer DVCAM / Raw
    - Works in Progress #27, 1989-03-03; MS208.008.002.087.00016; Thomas, S.; Kortelueg, A.; Scheuer, J.; Mulligan, Derek (Box 87)
      Maxell T120 M20 1/2 in./ Master
    - Panel Discussion: Collaboration, 1989-03-15; MS208.008.002.087.00017; Anthony, Carol; Rochlin, Julie; Millar, Alan; Williams, James; Rieger, John; Uchida, Bart; Berry, Ethan; Mulligan, Derek (Box 87)
      Maxell T120 M20 1/2 in.
    - Fed Reserve Tape 1 of 2, 1989-04-26; MS208.008.002.087.00018; Uchida, Bart (Box 87)
      Sony UmaticS KCS-20XBR 3/4 in
    - Fed Reserve Tape 2 of 2, 1989-04-26; MS208.008.002.087.00019; Uchida, Bart (Box 87)
    - Works in Progress #28, 1989-05-03; MS208.008.002.087.00020; Schutte, Leo; Witham, Betsy; Colby, Audrey; Stephans, Beth; Mulligan, Derek (Box 87)
      Maxell T120 M20 1/2 in
    - Works in Progress #28, 1989-05-05; MS208.008.002.087.00021; Minuchan, Jean; Goss, Robert; Thomas, Steve; Pugh, Mark; Schneider, Carol; Mulligan, Derek (Box 87)
    - Space Gallery Tape 1, 1989-05-16; MS208.008.002.088.00001; Uchida (Box 88)
      Sony UmaticS KCS-20XBR 3/4 in / Brockton
    - Space Gallery Tape 2, 1989-05-16; MS208.008.002.088.00002; Uchida (Box 88)
    - Space Gallery Tape 3, 1989-05-16; MS208.008.002.088.00003; Uchida (Box 88)
    - Green on the Green, 1989-06-24; MS208.008.002.088.00004; Arsem, Marilyn (Box 88)
      Maxell T120 1/2 in / Dub / Xfer 01.07.14 DVCAM / In Cohasset
    - Green on the Green in Cohasset, 1989-06-24; MS208.008.002.088.00005; Arsem, Marilyn; White Ean (Box 88)
      Maxell T120 1/2 in / Xfer 01.08.14 / In Cohasset
    - Silent Observations, 1989-08; MS208.008.002.088.00006; Davis, Meredith; Arsem, Marilyn (Box 88)
      1/2 on VHS / Window Dub
    - Document: Silent Observations, 1989-08; MS208.008.002.088.00007; Davis, Meredith; Arsem, Marilyn (Box 88)
      Sony KCS-20XBR 3/4 in / Copy / Xfer to DV 12/9/13
    - Document: Silent Observations, 1989-08; MS208.008.002.088.00008; Davis, Meredith (Box 88)